Office of the Dean, School of Dental Medicine Records UA154
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of the Dean, School of Dental Medicine Records
2000 -- 2010
1947 -- 2012
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of the Dean of the School of Dental Medicine
Campbell, Patricia
Executive Associate Dean - School of Dental Medicine
School of Dental Medicine
UA154
21.6 Linear Feet 18 boxes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into six series: Executive Associate Dean subject files; Accreditation files; Executive Faculty minutes; Standing Committee minutes; Office files; Other committee minutes.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts University School of Dental Medicine was established in 1868 as Boston Dental College. It was incorporated into Tufts College in 1899. Although founded as a school to educate students from New England, today Tufts is renowned throughout the United States and the world as a center for academic and clinical excellence. Tufts boasts over 6,900 alumni composed of individuals from all fifty states and thirty-nine countries. The majority of the alumni outside of the USA have completed an Advanced Education Certificate program. Students receive a comprehensive education emphasizing the importance of didactic coursework, clinical experience, and practice management that prepares them to enter the work force as confident, proficient clinicians.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains records of the Office of the Dean of the School of Dental Medicine and includes correspondence, meeting minutes, press releases, publications, reports (including annual reports), and subject files. The bulk of the material is dated from 2000 to 2010 and documents the School of Medicine's activities. Specific topics addressed include strategic planning initiatives, as well as decisions made by various committees—such as the Executive Faculty Committee—about topics such as curriculum development and student-specific issues.
Administration and Governance -- Planning, evaluation, policies & procedures; Administration and Governance -- Accreditation; Curriculum and Instruction -- Faculty
- Executive Associate Dean Subject Files, 1997 -- 2012; 2001 -- 2005; UA154.001; 9.6 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of subject files kept by the Executive Associate Dean within the Office of the Dean in the School of Dental Medicine.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged as an alphabetical run by accession.
  Conditions Governing Access
  75 years from the date of creation. 20 years from date of creation.
  - Annual strategic Planning Mtg, 2003 -- 2004; UA154.001.001.00001; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Dental continuing education group, 1997 -- 2002; UA154.001.001.00002; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Dental outcomes, 2000 -- 2001; UA154.001.001.00003; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Dental outcomes, 2001 -- 2002; UA154.001.001.00004; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Dental outcomes, 2002 -- 2003; UA154.001.001.00005; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Dental outcomes, 2003 -- 2004; UA154.001.001.00006; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Domestic violence grant, 2003; UA154.001.001.00007; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Dutko group, 2001; UA154.001.001.00008; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Education media center, 2000; UA154.001.001.00009; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Enrollment, 2003; UA154.001.001.00010; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Faculty practice, 2002 -- 2003; UA154.001.001.00011; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Faculty salaries, 1999 -- 2002; UA154.001.001.00012; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - Faculty salaries survey, 1997 -- 1998; UA154.001.001.00013; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Families first, 2001; UA154.001.001.00014; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Misc. outcomes, 2003 -- 2005; UA154.001.001.00015; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Misc. survey/OAC, 2003 -- 2005; UA154.001.001.00016; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - OAC definition, 2001 -- 2005; UA154.001.001.00017; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Outcome assessment minutes, 2003 -- 2005; UA154.001.001.00018; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Strategic planning 1 of 2, 2003 -- 2005; UA154.001.001.00019; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Strategic planning 2 of 2, 2003 -- 2005; UA154.001.001.00020; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Web central, 2001; UA154.001.001.00021; Patricia Campbell (Box 1)
  - Academic Council Meeting, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Academic calendar, 2008 -- 2009; UA154.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Academic planning, September, 2005; UA154.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - A-DEC Portland, OR, 2008; UA154.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - A-DEC Training Sessions, 2009; UA154.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Advanced Education in Esthetic Dentistry (AEED) Fellowship, 2006; UA154.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - AEED Scheduling Dr. H. Hirayama, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Mediouni, Zineb, Student AEED Program, 2006; UA154.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Al Wazzean, Alaaeddin, DMD. M.Sc. Estetic dentristry, 2008; UA154.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report TUSDM 2008 Draft and Build up, 2008 -- 2010; UA154.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - ARC/chairs meeting, 2007; UA154.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Arguello, Emileo, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - ARC: Mr. Bryan Thorp, 2007; UA154.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - VE: Rob Quigley ARC, 2008; UA154.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Assessment meeting, 2011; UA154.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Astratech, 2006 -- 2009; UA154.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Proposed audit: Seth Kornetsky, 2006 -- 2009; UA154.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Auditor's visit, 2006; UA154.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Audit of admissions system security controls, 2005; UA154.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Audit: Graduate Student TUSDM, 2010; UA154.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - axiUm Users Meeting, Vancouver BC, 2005; UA154.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Baenen, Michael, Chief of Staff for President Bacow, 2009; UA154.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Bank of America, 2007; UA154.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Bi Med Center, 2008; UA154.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Bogo [Bogis], John, 2007; UA154.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Bookstore Action Plan meeting, 2005; UA154.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Boston Public Health Agreement, 2007; UA154.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Brehm Lectureship, 2009; UA154.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Bridge Over Troubled Waters Resident/Student Program, 2005 -- 2006; UA154.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Candidates for Assoc. Dean Student Affairs, 2011; UA154.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - CEA #06-0172C, 2006; UA154.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - CE Course, 2011; UA154.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Clinic Fees, 2009; UA154.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Clinic Income, 2005 -- 2006; UA154.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - 6 Month Review - Clinic Income Group, 2006; UA154.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Clinic limits, 2006; UA154.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - CODA Mock Site visit, 2007; UA154.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Georgy Cohen Managing Editor Tufts Web Communications, 2008 -- 2009; UA154.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - TUSDM: Community Service Learning Externship Forum Vivian Stephen-Hicks, 2005; UA154.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Dr. Wolfe - Externship Program, 2004; UA154.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Conflict of Interest form and University Policy, 2009; UA154.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - CORE Facilities, 2010 -- 2011; UA154.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Corrao, Regina, 2010; UA154.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - Course materials kit and bookstore, 2006; UA154.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - Massachusetts Region Conferences on Pandemic Preparedness, 2006; UA154.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - Table top exercise Mock Crisis, 2009; UA154.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - Crisis management, 2007; UA154.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - Crisis management: pandemic preparedness, 2007; UA154.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
  - Critical incident/temporary relocation, 2006; UA154.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
  - CT Scaner, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.002.00050 (Box 2)
  - Curriculum Procedures Manual, 2005 -- 2006; UA154.001.002.00051 (Box 2)
  - Deferred maintence budget FY13-14, 2011; UA154.001.002.00052 (Box 2)
  - J. Del Rossi Consulting LLC, 2000 -- 2007; UA154.001.002.00053 (Box 2)
  - DDE MS Program, 2005; UA154.001.002.00054 (Box 2)
  - DDE Budget meeting Dr. Noshir Mehta, 2006; UA154.001.002.00055 (Box 2)
  - DHS 848 Redesign Project, 2010 -- 2011; UA154.001.002.00056 (Box 2)
  - Dental radiology examination patients, 2004; UA154.001.002.00057 (Box 2)
  - Dental school gifts, 2006; UA154.001.002.00058 (Box 2)
  - Dental students: Libya, 2011; UA154.001.002.00059 (Box 2)
  - Dentisply, 2008; UA154.001.002.00060 (Box 2)
  - Development discussions workshop for TUSDM Leaders, 2009; UA154.001.002.00061 (Box 2)
  - Devlin, Diane, 2006; UA154.001.002.00062 (Box 2)
  - Maria Gove Trinagale Development, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.002.00063 (Box 2)
  - HSC: dining advisory group, 2011; UA154.001.002.00064 (Box 2)
  - Diversity training, 2006; UA154.001.002.00065 (Box 2)
  - Doctor of Science in Pharmacology, 2009; UA154.001.002.00066 (Box 2)
  - Dick Doolin Clinic Processes, Production, Revenue numbers, 2006; UA154.001.002.00067 (Box 2)
  - Doff, Richard, 2010; UA154.001.002.00068 (Box 2)
  - Ed Dental Coverage at Beth Israel Deaconness Medical Center, 2007; UA154.001.002.00069 (Box 2)
  - Education Technology Directors Position, 2008; UA154.001.002.00070 (Box 2)
  - ELAM, 2010; UA154.001.002.00071 (Box 2)
  - Electronic PO Regs Signature Levels, 2009; UA154.001.002.00072 (Box 2)
  - Equipment, 2007; UA154.001.002.00073 (Box 2)
  - Endontics Faculty issues, 2004 -- 2009; UA154.001.002.00074 (Box 2)
  - Endodontics PG budget Profile FY2007, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.002.00075 (Box 2)
  - Endodontics: Current fiscal budget and projections for next fiscal budget, 2005 -- 2006; UA154.001.002.00076 (Box 2)
  - Security of P.G. Endo department of DHS 2, 2006; UA154.001.002.00077 (Box 2)
  - Enrollment planning, 2006; UA154.001.002.00078 (Box 2)
  - Executive Associate Dean, 2006 -- 2008; UA154.001.002.00079 (Box 2)
  - Executive VP Meeting, 2010; UA154.001.002.00080 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Development Position, 2009; UA154.001.002.00081 (Box 2)
  - Faclty III Calls, 2005 -- 2006; UA154.001.002.00082 (Box 2)
  - FEMA Training Presentation, 2007; UA154.001.002.00083 (Box 2)
  - 4th Year Focus Group, 2007; UA154.001.002.00084 (Box 2)
  - Gates Proposal, 2007; UA154.001.002.00085 (Box 2)
  - Geriatrics Meeting, 2009; UA154.001.002.00086 (Box 2)
  - Golden Crown Award, 2009; UA154.001.002.00087 (Box 2)
  - Grace Period Extension PG Prosthodontics, 2010; UA154.001.002.00088 (Box 2)
  - Grant Funding Beyond June 30, 2007, UA154.001.002.00089 (Box 2)
  - Hammer, Norman, 2009; UA154.001.002.00090 (Box 2)
  - FY12-14 Budget Dr Hanley, 2010; UA154.001.002.00091 (Box 2)
  - Dr. Charles Hapcook Eastern Dental Insurance Company, 2007; UA154.001.002.00092 (Box 2)
  - Massachusetts Division of Health Care Fiance and Policy, 2007; UA154.001.002.00093 (Box 2)
  - Herman, Aidee, 2006; UA154.001.002.00094 (Box 2)
  - Henry Schein/Midmark Jeff Blair and Mr. Jim Hammon, 2010; UA154.001.002.00095 (Box 2)
  - HSC: Crisis Management Team Meeting, 2007; UA154.001.002.00096 (Box 2)
  - Hock, Janet, 2010; UA154.001.002.00097 (Box 2)
  - Dr. Hsu - Alumni, 2008; UA154.001.002.00098 (Box 2)
  - IGI System Demo, 2009; UA154.001.002.00099 (Box 2)
  - Immigration Issues Dr. Moustafa, 2007; UA154.001.002.00100 (Box 2)
  - Implant Fellowship, 2009; UA154.001.002.00101 (Box 2)
  - Implant Center Fellowships and Budget for 08, 2007 -- 2008; UA154.001.002.00102 (Box 2)
  - Implant Program, 2005 -- 2009; UA154.001.002.00103 (Box 2)
  - Informatics Center Drs. Chapman, Russell, Stark, 2007; UA154.001.002.00104 (Box 2)
  - Institutional naming policies, 2007; UA154.001.002.00105 (Box 2)
  - iPods and teaching, 2008; UA154.001.002.00106 (Box 2)
  - IRB Training Predoc Students Dr. Chapman Dr. Stark, 2007; UA154.001.002.00107 (Box 2)
  - Jaharis Green Space, 2007 -- 2009; UA154.001.002.00108 (Box 2)
  - JINN-JAW, Shiow Pediatric Dentristry, 2007; UA154.001.002.00109 (Box 2)
  - Joanne Falzone, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.002.00110 (Box 2)
  - Job Descriptions, 2007; UA154.001.002.00111 (Box 2)
  - Dr. James F. Kane and Family Faculty Fund, 2006; UA154.001.002.00112 (Box 2)
  - Kanacosta, Olympia, 2006; UA154.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Keystone Software Presentation, 2008; UA154.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Keystone Dental, 2008 -- 2009; UA154.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Lee, Brian PG Prostho Resident, 2007; UA154.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Lee, Dennis (Patient), 2007 -- 2008; UA154.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - On-Line College, 2008 -- 2009; UA154.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Marty Oppenheimer General Counsel, 2008; UA154.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Oral Biology Equipment Request, 2005; UA154.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Oral Health in India Dr. Noshir Mehta, 2005 -- 2006; UA154.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Lisa Prior Consulting, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Dr. William Lobel, Director of Continuing Education Candidate, 2009; UA154.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - McManus, Joseph EAD: Grafton Campus, 2008 -- 2010; UA154.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Mail Room Renovations, 2009; UA154.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Mass Dental Society Payout, 2006; UA154.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Medical Board Meeting, 2005; UA154.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - M & V Laboratory Space, 2009; UA154.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Miller Scholarship, 2006; UA154.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - MRC/Ed Media Allocations/Fee Structure, 2008; UA154.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - National Museum of Dentistry: Dr. Samuel Harris, 2010; UA154.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - New England Baptist Hospital Compensation & Pay Practices, 2008; UA154.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Student Handpiece Kit, 2008; UA154.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Gendex, 2005 -- 2006; UA154.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Northeast Metropolitan Regional Vocational School Student Trainees, 2006; UA154.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - OMFR Practice Dr. A Ramesh & Dr. N. Mehta, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - O & M Allocations Boston Campus, 2000 -- 2001; UA154.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Orthodontics 2005, UA154.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Dr. Briss Orthodontics, 2005; UA154.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - Outcomes Assessment Committee Meeting Materials, 2010 -- 2011; UA154.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Patient and Other Complaints, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Patient Letter: A Jewell, 2009; UA154.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Patient Letters, 2008 -- 2011; UA154.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Patient Survey Instrument: Webinar, 2010; UA154.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Perio Salaries, 2006; UA154.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - Department of Periodontology: Staff Meeting, 2006; UA154.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - Perio Accreditation, 2007; UA154.001.003.00035 (Box 3)
  - Perio Alumni Event September 2009, UA154.001.003.00036 (Box 3)
  - Potential Satellite Clinic, 2008; UA154.001.003.00037 (Box 3)
  - Practice Coordinator: Duties & Responsibilities, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.003.00038 (Box 3)
  - PC Duties and Responsibilities, 2008; UA154.001.003.00039 (Box 3)
  - Pride Institute, 2005; UA154.001.003.00040 (Box 3)
  - Pride Institute Questionnaire Responses, 2005; UA154.001.003.00041 (Box 3)
  - PG Prosthodontics Center for Advanced Dental Technology, 2007; UA154.001.003.00042 (Box 3)
  - Research Strategy, 2008; UA154.001.003.00043 (Box 3)
  - Research Restructuring Meeting, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.003.00044 (Box 3)
  - Radiation Safety, 2006; UA154.001.003.00045 (Box 3)
  - Radiology Gendex, 2003 -- 2005; UA154.001.003.00046 (Box 3)
  - Radiology Kodak, 2005; UA154.001.003.00047 (Box 3)
  - Radiology Process, 2006; UA154.001.003.00048 (Box 3)
  - Radiology/NPE's Meeting, 2006; UA154.001.003.00049 (Box 3)
  - Radiology Incentive Arrangement, 2007 -- 2009; UA154.001.003.00050 (Box 3)
  - Reassignment of Chairs: Emergency, CPR and NPE, 2000 -- 2010; UA154.001.003.00051 (Box 3)
  - Regulatory Audit: USEPA, 2006; UA154.001.003.00052 (Box 3)
  - Renovations PreClin Increasing Seat Capacity, 2006; UA154.001.003.00053 (Box 3)
  - Research, 2001 -- 2009; UA154.001.003.00054 (Box 3)
  - Research Retreat March 29, 2007, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.003.00055 (Box 3)
  - Research Administration Job Description, 2004 -- 2005; UA154.001.003.00056 (Box 3)
  - Research Collaboration Dr. P. Damoulis, 2006; UA154.001.003.00057 (Box 3)
  - Research Department Progress Report, 2004 -- 2006; UA154.001.003.00058 (Box 3)
  - Informed Consent: Research Patients, 2006; UA154.001.003.00059 (Box 3)
  - Research, 2003; UA154.001.003.00060 (Box 3)
  - Rosati, Christine, 2008 -- 2011; UA154.001.003.00061 (Box 3)
  - Practice Management: Dr. Samaras, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.003.00062 (Box 3)
  - Saidah, Arthur, 2009; UA154.001.003.00063 (Box 3)
  - SAS Programmer Job Description, 2006 -- 2008; UA154.001.003.00064 (Box 3)
  - Sedation Center, 2007; UA154.001.003.00065 (Box 3)
  - Strategic Vision Statement, 2009; UA154.001.003.00066 (Box 3)
  - Strategic Talent Development: Development Discussion, 2010; UA154.001.003.00067 (Box 3)
  - Strategic Talent Development Committee, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.003.00068 (Box 3)
  - 75 Kneeland Street, 2008 -- 2009; UA154.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Signature Approval Meeting, 2008; UA154.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Simulation Lab, 2007 -- 2008; UA154.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Simulated Patient Care Issues & Proposals, 2005 -- 2006; UA154.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Software Purchases, 2005; UA154.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Space Planning--Boston, 2005 -- 2007; UA154.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Space Planning Octpber 24. 2000, 2000 -- 2004; UA154.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Space Planning--Classroom, 2004; UA154.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Stakeholders Working Group (Vision & Expectations Renovations), 2010; UA154.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Planning Retreat, 2008 -- 2010; UA154.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Planning Retreat 5/12/11, 2011; UA154.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Planning, 2010; UA154.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Important [Strategic Planning Retreat], 2009; UA154.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Planning Hyatt 4/8/2010, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Planning Retreat February 2007, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Planning Retreat April 24, 2008 Hyatt Regency Hotel, UA154.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Planning Retreat April 9, 2009, UA154.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Planning, 2008 -- 2009; UA154.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Planning Retreat, 2002 -- 2004; UA154.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Strategic Planning Survey Results, 2009; UA154.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Student Assignments in Clinic, 2007; UA154.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Student Dress Code, 2007; UA154.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Student Transportation to Off-Site Locations, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Succession Planning, 2009; UA154.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Succession Planning 2006, UA154.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Sullivan Lauretta, TDA: Oral Surgery Billing Coordinator, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Space/TCM, 2010; UA154.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Supplier Presentations, 2009; UA154.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - 23rd Annual Conference on Teaching and Learning, 2009; UA154.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - TUSDM Periodontology Clinic Operations Audit January 2005, 2006; UA154.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Technology Committee, Facilitator Dr. Roger Galburt, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Thibeault, Peter: Automatic Voice Self Pay Collection Program, 2009; UA154.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Third (3rd) Floor Renovations 2006, UA154.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Expedia, 2004 -- 2010; UA154.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - TDF Dental Assistants, 2008; UA154.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - TDF Xiaojing, Li, 2009; UA154.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Medical Center Smoking Policy, 2010; UA154.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Medical Center Smoking Policy, 2009; UA154.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
  - Tuition Reduction for American Trained Students, 2005; UA154.001.004.00039 (Box 4)
  - UCCPS Faculty Fellow Funding, 2005 -- 2007; UA154.001.004.00040 (Box 4)
  - Unionization Efforts Meeting, 2007 -- 2009; UA154.001.004.00041 (Box 4)
  - OAC Meeting Minutes, 2008 -- 2009; UA154.001.004.00042 (Box 4)
  - OAC Meeting October 17, 2005, 2005 -- 2008; UA154.001.004.00043 (Box 4)
  - USDA Jean Mayer HNRCA, 2008; UA154.001.004.00044 (Box 4)
  - Virtual Seminar: Principles and Practices of Effective Faculty, 2007; UA154.001.004.00045 (Box 4)
  - Web Content Specialist Job Description, 2006; UA154.001.004.00046 (Box 4)
  - Cosgrove, Suzanne L. Web Content Specialist, 2009; UA154.001.004.00047 (Box 4)
  - Davis, Gregory Web Content Specialist, 2009; UA154.001.004.00048 (Box 4)
  - DeRocher, Stephen Web Content Specialist, 2009; UA154.001.004.00049 (Box 4)
  - Nguyen, Kenny, 2009; UA154.001.004.00050 (Box 4)
  - Pena, Joel Web Content Specialist, 2009; UA154.001.004.00051 (Box 4)
  - Tardi, Carla Web Content Specialist, 2009; UA154.001.004.00052 (Box 4)
  - Helfman, Amy Web Content Specialist, 2009; UA154.001.004.00053 (Box 4)
  - Brady, Joseph Web Content Specialist, 2009; UA154.001.004.00054 (Box 4)
  - Web Content Specialist Resumes, 2009; UA154.001.004.00055 (Box 4)
  - Sub Committee Web Development Facilitator: Dr. Roger Galburt, 2006; UA154.001.004.00056 (Box 4)
  - Website Development and Updating, 2005; UA154.001.004.00057 (Box 4)
  - Xavier Associates, 2007; UA154.001.004.00058 (Box 4)
  - Yong, Kim, 2006; UA154.001.004.00059 (Box 4)
  - Cadicam Equipment Dallas Texas, 2010; UA154.001.004.00060 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Survey, 2003 -- 2004; UA154.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Austin,Elizabeth Web Content Specialist, 2008 -- 2009; UA154.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Dr. Tsamtsouris Agreement, 2000; UA154.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Dr. Robert Chapman, Chair Prosthodontics and Operative Dentistry, 2009; UA154.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Endo G/O, 2000 -- 2010; UA154.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - General Dentistry G/O, 2004; UA154.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Oral Surgery G/O, 2004; UA154.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Oral Path Surgery G/O, 2005; UA154.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Pedo G/O OAC, 2003; UA154.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Perio G/O OAC, 2005; UA154.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Prostho and Operative G/O OAC, 2004; UA154.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Doherty, Eileen, 2005; UA154.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Driscoll, Stephen, 2004; UA154.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Miller, Mel, 2004 -- 2005; UA154.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Morgan, John, 2004; UA154.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Nopsaran Chaimattayompol (Dr. Nui), 2004 -- 2005; UA154.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Athena Papas, 2004; UA154.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Rudy, Robert, 2005; UA154.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Salvnier, 2005; UA154.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Hudo Stipho, 2004; UA154.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Dr. Karen Chang-Yeh, 2005; UA154.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Mary Elizabeth Pierce, 2004; UA154.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Janine Fredericks-Younger, 2004; UA154.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - [Damoulis], 2004; UA154.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - General Systems Designs, 2004; UA154.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Clinic Implementation, 2004; UA154.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - DSI, 1998 -- 2003; UA154.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Tarek Ashmawy, 2004; UA154.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Bookless, 2005; UA154.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - D'Innocenzo, 2005; UA154.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Information Tech. Objectives OAC, 2004; UA154.001.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Research G/O OAC, 2003; UA154.001.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Clinical Faculty Evaluations, 2005; UA154.001.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Goals/Objectives -OA, 2004; UA154.001.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Academic Affairs G/O, 2003; UA154.001.005.00035 (Box 5)